dressupdollgames.net 2011-03-20

# Dress Up Doll Games - Privacy Policy

**Guests**  
We do not collect any personal information on this website. However, our web server logs all visitor information and we use this for statistical purposes.

**Members**  
Your profile information will be available to anyone who chooses to view it. Do not put sensitive personal information in your profile. We will not share your e-mail address with anyone. It will be used to send you site news and newsletters. You may opt-out of these at any time once you've logged into the site.  
**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, and Widgetbucks. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

**
